B: Sorry I’m late.
M: Don’t worry, Ben.
We haven’t ordered yet.
We were waiting for you.
You have something on your tie.
B: I do? Oh.
It’s from work.
Thanks.
W: Are you ready to order?
M: Yes, please.
W: Can I get you something to start with?
M: OK.
Do we want starters?
No, thank you.
I’d like the tuna.
W: Would you like that with salad or chips?
M: Salad, please.
W: And for you?
I: I’ll have the steak, please.
W: How would you like your steak?
Rare, medium, or well done?
I: Rare.
W: And for you?
The tuna for you, the steak for you.
The other dishes are coming.
M: Excuse me.
I asked for salad, not chips.
W: Oh, I’m sorry.
No problem, I’ll change it.
M: Thank you.
I: Excuse me.
W: Yes?
I: I asked for my steak rare, and this is medium.
W: I’m really sorry.
I’ll take it back to the kitchen.
M: Can we have the bill, please?
W: Of course.
M: I think there’s a mistake here.
I had the salad, not chips.
And Izzy had the steak.
W: I’m very sorry.
I’ll change that.